Find your voice.
Moxie is a comedy, drama, music film directed by Amy Poehler.
Inspired by her mom's rebellious past and a confident new friend, a shy
16-year-old publishes an anonymous zine calling out sexism at her school.
Vivian Carter, played by Hadley Robinson.
Claudia, played by Lauren Tsai.
Lucy Hernandez, played by Alycia Pascual-Peña.
Seth Acosta, played by Nico Hiraga.
Kaitlynn Price, played by Sabrina Haskett.
Mitchell Wilson, played by Patrick Schwarzenegger.
Moxie (stylized as MOXiE!) is a 2021 American
comedy-drama film directed by Amy Poehler.
Tamara Chestna and Dylan Meyer adapted the screenplay from the
2017 novel of the same name by Jennifer Mathieu.
It stars Hadley Robinson, Alycia Pascual-Peña, Lauren Tsai,
Patrick Schwarzenegger, Nico Hiraga, and Poehler.
The film focuses on 16-year-old Vivian (played by Hadley Robinson), who starts a feminist zine to empower the
young women in her high school, as they contend with bullying, sexual harassment, and rape.
The film was released on March 3, 2021, by Netflix and
received mixed-to-positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of based on novel or
book, woman director, inspirational.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.